<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on PSTT Knowledge Base</title><link>/teetimes/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on PSTT Knowledge Base</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/teetimes/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recommended Hardware</title><link>/teetimes/getting-started/recommended-hardware/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/teetimes/getting-started/recommended-hardware/</guid><description>Overview linkProshop Tee Times will run on just about any Windows computer and is compatible with almost all touch screen monitors, receipt printers, cash drawers, barcode scanners, etc. If you have existing hardware it is very likely that you will not need to purchase anything new.
If you are looking to upgrade or purchase new equipment our recommendations can be found below.
The following links are all from Amazon for easy ordering, however most of this equipment can be purchased from other locations if you find a better deal from a seller you trust.</description></item><item><title>Windows Installation</title><link>/teetimes/getting-started/windows-installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/teetimes/getting-started/windows-installation/</guid><description>report Please Note: Our software installation requires a passcode. Before proceeding be sure to email support@pstt.golf or contact your support representative for that passcode.
Download link Click on this link or visit https://pstt.golf/download in the web browser of your choice. You should end up on our &amp;lsquo;Install Proshop Tee Times&amp;rsquo; page. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to grant us remote access to your computer for technical support click on the icon above &amp;lsquo;Proshop Tee Times &amp;amp; STS&amp;rsquo;, this is our recommended version.</description></item><item><title>Mac Installation</title><link>/teetimes/getting-started/mac-installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/teetimes/getting-started/mac-installation/</guid><description>report Please Note: Accessing Proshop Tee Times on a Mac requires remote control software of a remote Windows PC. Due to this setup some features such as credit card processing, receipt printing, cash drawer control are not possible.
Introduction linkPlease make sure you have received remote login credentials from our staff. If you need credentials please click here to email support@pstt.golf or contact your support representative.
Install Microsoft Remote Desktop link First we need to install Microsoft Remote Desktop from the App Store on your Mac.</description></item><item><title>PSTT Admin Mobile App</title><link>/teetimes/getting-started/pstt-admin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/teetimes/getting-started/pstt-admin/</guid><description>About linkPSTT Admin allows for limited mobile management of your course on your smart phone. You can view the tee sheet, update your public current conditions, view reports, and more. Install PSTT Admin link Click this link on your mobile device or search your app store for &amp;lsquo;PSTT Admin&amp;rsquo;.
Click the download or install button to install the PSTT Admin app. Setup link Launch the PSTT Admin app on your mobile device.</description></item></channel></rss>