<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Golf Genius TM on PSTT Knowledge Base</title><link>/apps/golfgenius/</link><description>Recent content in Golf Genius TM on PSTT Knowledge Base</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/apps/golfgenius/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/apps/golfgenius/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apps/golfgenius/introduction/</guid><description>Integration Requirements linkThis feature is only available when paired with either of the following Golf Genius Tournament Management products:
Features link Master Roster Sync: Golf Genius Tournament Management will automatically import your Proshop Tee Times contacts into your master roster on a nightly basis.
Event Portal Shortcuts: Automatically provides access to Golf Genius Tournament Management events, allowing quick and easy access to registration and events within your app.
Single Sign-On: If using both of the above features, your members can then register for Golf Genius Tournament Management events without being required to sign in and without being required to provide their contact information each time.</description></item><item><title>Setup &amp; Onboarding</title><link>/apps/golfgenius/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apps/golfgenius/setup/</guid><description>Step 1 - Check Requirements linkPlease verify that you are using one of Golf Genius Tournament Management&amp;rsquo;s premium products which support mobile score entry:
Step 2 - Contact Us linkPlease send an email to apps@pstt.golf and request that we enable the Golf Genius Tournament Management integration for your course.
You should expect this process to take a few days. We will get back to you with an email address to use in Step 3.</description></item><item><title>Master Roster Sync</title><link>/apps/golfgenius/roster-sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apps/golfgenius/roster-sync/</guid><description>Introduction linkMaster roster sync is an optional feature in which your Proshop Tee Times contacts are automatically imported into your Golf Genius Tournament Management master roster on a nightly basis. Taking advantage of master roster sync will save you time when creating events, as you will not have to enter contact information for each of your players.
Setup linkOnce your Golf Genius Tournament Management integration has been setup and activated please email apps@pstt.</description></item><item><title>Event Portal Shortcuts</title><link>/apps/golfgenius/event-portals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apps/golfgenius/event-portals/</guid><description>User Experience linkYour mobile app will have designated areas in which Golf Genius Tournament Management event portal shortcuts can appear. Users can tap on event shortcuts to access the event portal. From the event portal they can sign up or manage their registration for an event, view event details, check out the leaderboards, final results, and more.
Adding Shortcuts linkThe following steps will walk you through displaying a Golf Genius Tournament Management event portal shortcut within your mobile app.</description></item><item><title>Mobile Score Entry</title><link>/apps/golfgenius/mobile-score-entry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/apps/golfgenius/mobile-score-entry/</guid><description>User Experience link Golf Genius Tournament Management events which are configured for mobile score entry will appear on the home screen of your app. Tapping on these events will open the player selection window. Players will locate tap on their name in the event&amp;rsquo;s player list. Your players will have the opportunity to see their team, starting hole, tee time, handicap, and other event information. (Not Pictured) They will then press continue to load the scorecard.</description></item></channel></rss>